bahamasb2b.com 2002-12-17

# Privacy

**BahamasB2B.com Privacy Policy**  
Effective August 22, 2000

**Our Commitment To Privacy  **  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on most pages of our site and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:**    
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the BahamasB2B.com website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name   
Address   
Email address   
Phone number   
Credit, Debit Card or Check Information 

On the Discussion Forum page we collect the IP number of the computer you are using to identify the computer being used to ensure that no one is using another person's name or pretending to be someone else.

**The Way We Use Information:  **  
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

You can register with our website if you would like to receive our newsletter as well as the full range of member's discounts and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

We use WebTrends Live to conduct anonymous web traffic analysis for our site. While WebTrends Live makes use of cookies, no personal information is ever collected or analyzed by this service. For more information on WebTrends Live, please visit their site at:  
http://www.webtrendslive.com/privacy_policy.htm.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security:  **  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:**    
You can request all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by emailing us at webmaster@bahamasb2b.com. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us:**    
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 242-394-0033 or send us an email at [lisa@bahamasb2b.com](mailto:lisa@bahamasb2b.com).
